

YUSRIL S KAIMUDIN

0813-8417-7246 / yusril.sk2000@gmail.com / Agung Raya II St. Lenteng Agung, South Jakarta

PROFILE

Fresh graduate with extensive experience in the field of Information Technology. Despite being a fresh graduate, I have acquired substantial work experience that has honed my skills. With the capabilities and knowledge I have gained, I am confident in my ability to work diligently and complete tasks efficiently, as it has become a guiding principle in my life.

EDUCATION

· Junior High School

Nurush Shafaat Lele Islamic (2012-2015)

· Senior High School

Al-Khairaat Islamic, Bibinoi Boarding School (2015-2018)

· Bachelor of Technology

Institute of Business and Informatics Kosgoro 1957 (2018-2022)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Implementor IT & Software Support

PT Bengawan Cable Vision (2021-2022)

- · Supervising programmers in the development of the SIPLah, adasemua.com website.
- Monitoring servers.
- Conducting User Acceptance Testing (UAT) on the website.
- Providing corrections to the website development flow if it doesn't align with the requirements
- · Presenting a progress report on the website during the meeting.

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

- General Secretary of the Islamic Boarding School Organization (2017-2018)
- Head of Islamic Studies Department, Islamic Propagation Student Association (2018-2020)
- Member of the Indonesian Islamic Student Action Union (KAMMI) (2018-2020)
- General Secretary of the Association of Islamic Students (HMI) Kom IBI-Kosgoro 1957 (2020-2021)
- Chairman of the Student Executive Board (BEM) of Kosgoro 1957 Business & Informatics Institute (2021-2022)
- Central Executive Board Member of the Nusantara Student Executive Board (BEMNUS) (2022-2023)
- Member of the Islamic Student Association (HMI) Depok Branch (2022-2024)

EXPERTISE

HARD SKILL

- Backend
- Front End
- MySQL & XAMPP
- · Microsoft Office

SOFT SKILL

- Leadership
- Time Management and Responsibility
- · Disciplined, Creative, and Innovative
- · Adaptive, Teamwork and Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- Indonesia
- English

COVER LETTER

Dear HR.

Please accept my resume for an application at your company. As a student who has graduated from Informatics of Technic, and has approximately 1 year experience in IT Support.

Being a student at IBI Kosgoro 57, maintaining perfect grades is the most important thing for me. My background in computer science and extensive experience in administration has taught me to be disciplined and focused with my responsibilities, this is a quality that is needed by all professionals in the workforce. My experience working in a group environment has also instilled the values of cooperation.

As a junior programmer with experience, I have developed skills in computer programming and software development. However, I also have substantial experience in administration. Over the years of involvement in various organizations, I have gained valuable experience in managing documents, scheduling meetings, and interacting with Microsoft Office applications. Additionally, I have good communication skills and can work effectively in teams. I am able to interact with people from diverse backgrounds, enabling me to collaborate effectively and contribute in a diverse work environment.

As a member of the group, I also contribute in raising morale, enthusiasm, and innovation in expressing opinions. Through all my efforts as an employee, it is proven that I am an enthusiastic and dedicated person in everything I do.

I would love to be part of your company. I want to develop my abilities and contribute to your company.

Thank you for taking the time to read this cover letter and I would love to hear from you.

KIND REGARDS,

YUSRIL S KAIMUDIN

AMPIRAN-LAMPIRAN

SERTIFIKAT IJAZAH

Gelar

Tanggal Kelulusan Place and Date of Birth Tempat dan Tanggal Lahii

Date of Judicium

The degree of

Nomor Seri Ijazah: 552012022000570 Register Number



Accredited by National Accreditation Baend For Higher Education Akreditasi BAN - PT No : 155/SK/BAN-PT/Akred/PT/IV/2019

INSTITUT BISNIS DAN INFORMATIKA KOSGORO 1957

INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS & INFORMATICS KOSGORO 1957 (IBI-K57)

Hereby confers upon Dengan ini memberikan kepada

YUSRIL S. KAIMUDIN

Student Registration Number NPM. 05201840007

National Identity Number NIK. 8204190101010001

Lele, 1 Januari 2000 Lele, January 1st, 2000

13 Agustus 2022

August 13th, 2022

SARJANA KOMPUTER (S.Kom) **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Program Studi Teknik Informatika Fakultas Ilmu Komputer

With all the rights and reponsibilties related to this academic degree Beserta segala hak dan tanggung jawab yang melekat pada gelar akademik ini

Rector of IBI-K57 Rektor IBI-K57

Dr. Haswan Yunaz, M.M., M.Si





Jakarta, 22 Agustus 2022 Dekan

Dean



INSTITUT BISNIS DAN INFORMATIKA KOSGORO 1957

TRANSKRIP AKADEMIK ACADEMIC TRANSCRIPT

Nomor: 05202213080285

Nama Mahasiswa	: YUSRIL S. KAIMUDIN	Fakultas	: FAKULTAS ILMU KOMPUTER
<i>Name</i>		Faculty	FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE
NPM	: 05201840007	Program Studi	: TEKNIK INFORMATIKA
Registration Number		Study Program	TECHNICAL INFORMATION
Tempat dan Tanggal I Place, Date of Birth	Lahir: Lele, 01/01/2000	Peminatan Concentration	

NO	KODE MK Course Code	KODE MK NAMA MATA KULIAH SKS course Code Course Credit		NR.Al Grade		MUTU Point	NO	KODE MK Course Code	NAMA MATA KULIAH	SKS Credit	NILAI Grade	ANGKA Score	MUTU Point
1	BIK 1001	Pendidikan Agama Religious Education	2	A	4,00	8	23	TI 4023	Pemrograman Berorientasi Obyek (Java Ide) Object Oriented Programming (Java Ide)	4	٨	4.00	16
2	IBIK 1002	Bahasa Indonesia Indonesian	2	A	4.00	8	24	T1 4024	Pemrograman Web 2 (Php) Web Programming 2 (Php)	4	8-	2,75	11
3	IBIK 1003	Pendidikan Pancasila Pencasile Education	2	A	4,00	8	25	TI 4025	Bahasa Inggris II English II	. 2	8	3,00	6
4	TI 1004	Logika & Algoritma Logic & Algorithm	4	В	3.00	12	26	TI 5026	Keamanan Teknologi Informasi Information Technology Security	3	A	4.00	12
5	TI 1005	Algoritma & Struktur Data (C++ Fund) Algorithms & Date Structures (C++ Fund)	4	A-	3.75	15	27	TI 5027	Sistem Operasi Operating system	4	٨	4.00	16
6	TI 1006	Pengantar Tek, Informasi & Kom. Introduction Tech. Information & Com.	3	٨	4.00	12	28	TI 5028	Rangkalan Digital Digital Circuit	3	B+	3.25	9.75
7	IBIK 2007	Kewarganegaraan Chrics	2	A	4.00	8	29	TI 5029	Troubleshooting (desktop dan hardware) Troubleshooting (desktop and hardware)	4	С	2.00	8
8	IBIK 2008	Kekosgoroan Kekosgoroan	2	A-	3.75	7.5	30	TI 5030	Statistika Statistics	3	A	4.00	12
9	TI 2009	Enterpreneurship Enterpreneurship	3	A	4.00	12	31	TI 5031	Metode Numerik Numerical Method	3	C+	2,25	6.75
10	TI 2010	Arsitektur & Organisasi Komputer Computer Architecture & Organization	4	A	4,00	16	32	TI 6032	Database (Fundamental)-1 Database (Fundamental)-1	4	8-	2,75	11
11	TI 2011	Perancangan Basis Data Detabase Design	4	A	4.00	16	33	TI 6033	Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak Software Engineering	4	A	4.00	16
12	TI 2012	Aljabar Linier Linear Aljabar	3	B-	2.75	8,25	34	TI 6034	Wireless dan Mobile Computing Wireless dan Mobile Computing	3	٨-	3,75	11,25
13	TI 3013	Interaksi Manusia & Komputer Human & Computer Interaction	3	A	4.00	12	35	TI 6035	Metode Penelitian Research methods	3	٨	4.00	12
14	TI 3014	Matematika Diskrit Discrete Mathematics	3	^	4.00	12	36	TI 6036	Data warehouse Data warehouse	3	C+	2.25	6.75
15	TI 3015	Kecakapan Antar Personal	2	A-	3.75	7.5	37	TI 6037	Teknologi Antar Jaringan Inter Network Technology	4	A	4.00	16
16	TI 3016	Jaringan Komputer (Fundamental) Computer Networking (Fundamental)	4	A	4.00	16	38	TI 7038	Database 2 (Lanjutan) Database 2 (Lanjutan)	4	B+	3.25	13
17	TI 3017	Pemrograman Java Dasar Basic Java Programming	4	A	4.00	16	39	TI 7039	Kuliah Kerja Praktek Prectical Work Lecture	4	B+	3.25	13
18	TI 3018	Pemrograman Web 1 (Html+Cas) Web Programming 1 (Html+Css)	- 14	A	4.00	16	40	TI 7040	Audit Tata Kelola It If Governance Audit	4	A-	3.75	15
19	TI 3019	Bahasa Inggris I English I	2	B+	3.25	6.5	41	TI 7041	Manajemen Proyek Sistem Informasi System Project Management Information	4	B+	3.25	13
20	TI 4020	Etika Profesi (Anti Korupsi) Professional Ethics (Anti Corruption)	3	A-	3.75	11,25	42	TI 7042	Pemrograman Perangkat Mobile Mobile Device Programming	4	B-	2.75	11
21	TI 4021	Jaringan Komputer Lanjut Advanced Computer Network	4	B-	2.75	11	43	INF 801	Tugas Akhir Theais	6	A	4.00	24
22	TI 4022	Pemrograman Visual (Net Framework) Visual Programming (Net Framework)	4	C+	2.25	9		WI					

Total SKS yang ditempuh Credit Earned

: 3.50

Indeks Prestasi Kumulatif Grade Point Average

Yudisium Judiclum

: Sangat Memuaskan Very Setisfactory

Skripsi: Rancang Bangun Aplikasi Presensi Online Menggunakan Qr Code Dengan Algoritma Vige Cipher Berbasis Websita Studi Kasus Sekolah Dasar Islam Terpadu (SD IT) Alkiyan

Thesis:
Design and Build Online Presence Applications Using Qr Code With Website-Based Vi
Cipher Algorithm Case Study of Alklyan Integrated Islamic Elementary School (SD IT)

Rektor Rector

Dr. HASWAN YUNAZ, M.M., M.SI.



lakarta, 22 Agustus 2022

Boy Firmansyah, S.Kom., M.Kom





Certificate of Completion No. 52.10/IBI-K57/283/06/22

As acknowledged by the Ministry of Education under Registration No. 421.9/1758 - DISDIK/ 08

This certificate is awarded to

Yusril S Kaimudin

NPM

05201840007

Study Program

Informatics

For completing TOEFL Paper Based Test with the following scores

as estion!	SCORE			
SECTION	Raw	Converted		
Listening Comprehension	17	42		
Structure and Written Expression	16	40		
Reading Comprehension	36	52		
TOEFL SCORE	447			

Jakarta, June 20th, 2022

Budi Djohari, S.E Managing Director of ILP Sawangan

Head of Language and Professional Development Department of IBI - K57

TOEFL is a registered trademark of Educational Testing Services (ETS) There is no relationship between ILP and ETS does not endorse this test



PRE VINSI MALUKU UTARA KABUPATEN HALMAHERA SELATAN

NIK : 8204190101010001

YUSRIL S. KAIMUDIN Tempat/Tgl Lahir : LELE, 01-01-2000

Jenis kelamin LAKI LAKI Gol. Darah :-

Namat LELE

HT/RW : 000/000

Kel/Desa : LELE Alamat

Kecamatan : MANDEDLI SELATAN

ISLAM Agama

Status Perkawnan: BELUM KAWIN

Pekerjaan : PELAJAR/MAHASISWA

Kewarganegaraan: WNI

Berlaku Hingga SEUMUR HIDUP



HALMAHERA SELATAN 01-04-2024

